<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PhaseWorm</title>
    <link>https://phaseworm.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on PhaseWorm</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://phaseworm.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>0.3.0</title>
      <link>https://phaseworm.com/patch-notes/0.3.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phaseworm.com/patch-notes/0.3.0/</guid>
      <description>After over 2 years of silence, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to announce another new feature release which takes the game from 0.2.x to 0.3.x. That&amp;rsquo;s right, PhaseWorm development has restarted!
  New Features!
 Xbox and Gamepad controller support! Xinput controller should be automatically detected and usable in the game&amp;rsquo;s engine with no additional configuration needed. Quick restart! Press ` (tilde) or the select / back button on your Xbox controller to instantly restart any level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0.2.2</title>
      <link>https://phaseworm.com/patch-notes/0.2.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phaseworm.com/patch-notes/0.2.2/</guid>
      <description>Refactored all scenes in Unity with a base resolution of 1920x1080, rather than 800x600 (ie: a 16:9 default instead of a 4:3 default). This should correct an issue with ultrawide resolutions (tested with 2560x1080) while menuing.
  Changed algorithm for in-game dynamic scaling of screen size to support ultra widescreen resolutions as well as 4:3. This means two algorithms are used, and we always then choose the one which is more zoomed out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0.2.1</title>
      <link>https://phaseworm.com/patch-notes/0.2.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phaseworm.com/patch-notes/0.2.1/</guid>
      <description> Fixed a bug which caused sound settings not to persist if the application was restarted.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0.2.0</title>
      <link>https://phaseworm.com/patch-notes/0.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phaseworm.com/patch-notes/0.2.0/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m excited to announce the new feature release which takes the game from 0.1.x to 0.2.x.
  9 Steam achievements!
 Problematic Practice - Eat the 14th and 15th apples in The Enchanted Forest without leaving the water. Winning Worm - Complete story mode. Proclaimer - Worm 1000 tiles. Shun Goku Satsu - Die 1000 deaths. Medal Meddler - Get a medal on any non-tutorial level. Medal Master - Get a medal on every level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speedrun.com Leaderboard</title>
      <link>https://phaseworm.com/announcements/speedrun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phaseworm.com/announcements/speedrun/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m excited to announce that today PhaseWorm comes to speedrun.com with an official game leaderboard! PhaseWorm was built for speedrunning, and so I&amp;rsquo;ve also included a livesplit autosplitter for release with the game. Just add this component into livesplit and the game will track your in-game time.
Even if you don&amp;rsquo;t want to use livesplit, you can speedrun phaseworm - the in-game timer will give you your final time and death count when you roll credits!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0.1.8</title>
      <link>https://phaseworm.com/patch-notes/0.1.8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phaseworm.com/patch-notes/0.1.8/</guid>
      <description> Added a new feature by user request which gives more feedback on the death screen. Players will now see the color of their worm at time of death, and the object they collided.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0.1.7</title>
      <link>https://phaseworm.com/patch-notes/0.1.7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phaseworm.com/patch-notes/0.1.7/</guid>
      <description> Fixed a minor typo in the Unity properties for Level 27 - &amp;ldquo;Intersections in Real Time&amp;rdquo; which was causing it not to log player deaths or medals on this stage. Level 25 - &amp;ldquo;Lake Rancid&amp;rdquo; contained a red apple on a brick tile. This was changed to the usual green apple for visiblity reasons.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Launch Day</title>
      <link>https://phaseworm.com/announcements/release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phaseworm.com/announcements/release/</guid>
      <description>Today is the day! PhaseWorm is officially released on Steam kicking off with the early bird gets the PhaseWorm sale. For one week only there will be 25% off of the baseline price.
Launch day also marks the opening of the Steam community page. Because this is an early access title, I invite everyone to use it to talk about what kind of experience you are all having with the various levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0.1.6</title>
      <link>https://phaseworm.com/patch-notes/0.1.6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phaseworm.com/patch-notes/0.1.6/</guid>
      <description> Added new control scheme for &amp;ldquo;Relative&amp;rdquo; controls. This allows the player to turn 90 degrees with the left and right arrow keys. The default controls are now labeled as &amp;ldquo;Absolute&amp;rdquo;.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0.1.5</title>
      <link>https://phaseworm.com/patch-notes/0.1.5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phaseworm.com/patch-notes/0.1.5/</guid>
      <description> Created in-game options for resolution and fullscreen adjustments.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early Access Trailer</title>
      <link>https://phaseworm.com/announcements/trailer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phaseworm.com/announcements/trailer/</guid>
      <description>Introducing PhaseWorm! PhaseWorm is a fast-paced 2D timing and reflex game built with a speedrunning focus. Players will be challenged to think and act quickly as they push for faster times and more difficult paths through each of the game&amp;rsquo;s 30 unique thematic stages.
Watch the early access trailer to learn more about PhaseWorm:
  PhaseWorm will be available on Steam starting May 4th!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
